Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 7: Grounds and Buildings, 1701-1982; 12 boxes; 2 items
  - Structural, 1944; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Plaque, stone missing. "This stone from the Houses of Parliament was presented to Princeton University by His Britannic Majesty's Government\u2026"
  - Structural, Undated; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Portion of a metal bracket. Unknown origin.
  - Structural, Undated; 1 box (Box D.2)
    Charred wood. Campus fire? Unknown building.
  - Structural, circa 1921-1930; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Bits of stone from McCormick? Hall.
    Steve Ofus '72, name on envelope.
  - Structural, circa 1701-1800; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Nails from Nassau Hall.
  - Structural, circa 1701-1800; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Slate from roof of Nassau Hall.
  - Structural, circa 1701-1800; 1 box (Box D.2)
    Box of assorted nails, keys, stone. "Nassau Hall Attic" on box.
  - Structural, Undated; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Key from Nassau Hall pre-1923.
    EX5011
    Gift of David Hume.
  - Structural, circa 1775-1783; circa 1861-1865; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Bullets. From Revolutionary War and Civil War excavated from the Princeton area.
    given by Pick Point Enterprises. Letter enclosed.
  - Structural, 1950 May 19; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Rope. Used by President Dodds to ring new Nassau Hall bell dedicated on May 19, 1950.
    Dr Chas. D Hart '92.
  - Structural, circa 1833; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Brick molds. Used for construction of East College.
    Presented by L E Hutchinson
  - Structural, 1868-1869; 1 box (Box D.1)
    "Fragment of the door of the Old Chapel, broken in an attempt to silence the bell. Class of 1870 sophomore year." (from the slip attached to the item; "See P82.01.869, p. 43)
    Class of 1870
    H. H. Savage (1904)
  - Trowel, 1903; 1 box (Box D.3)
    "This trowel was used by Woodrow Wilson October 16, 1903 to lay the corner stone of this building erected by the Class of 1879." (1879 Hall)
- Series 8: Medals, 1765-2010; 12 boxes
  This series contians medals related to Princeton University.
  - 15th reunion medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Orange and round, plastic; "92" "Quindecennial Reunion" in black; orange and black bow.
  - 20th reunion medal, 1912; 1 box (Box E.7)
    EX4115
    Gold and irregularly shaped; Princeton seal in orange and black, "1892," "1912" engraved; orange and black ribbon with "92" in gold; gold pin with "Vigesimal" engraved.
  - 25th reunion medal, 1917; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze. Round with Princeton seal, a tiger, "Princeton University," "Class of 1892" engraved; an orange and black ribbon with "'92" in golden; a pin engraved with "Twenty Fifth Reunion."
  - 40th reunion medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold and irregularly shaped; engraved "Princeton University 1929"; a black round plaque inset at center with "Fortieth Reunion 1889" engraved; orange and black ribbon.
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4815
    Cliosophic Society Badge. Eight pointed star. "Cliosoph Soc. Inst. MDCCLXV" and "Prodesse Quam Conspici."
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4811
    Cliosophic Society Badge. Eight pointed star. "Clios Soc. Instituta A.D. MDCCLXV" and "Prodesse Quam Conspici."
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4580
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4437
    Cliosophic Society Badge. Eight pointed star. "Clios. Soc. Instituta A.D. MDCCLXV" and "Prodesse Quam Conspici."
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4254
    Cliosophic Society Badge. Eight pointed star. "Cliosoph Soc. Inst. MDCCLXV; Wm S. Shields Class of 58; Prodesse Quam Conspici" inscribed on it.
    Class of 1858
  - Badge, Undated; 1 box (Box E.12)
    Cliosophic Society Badge. Eight pointed star. "Cliosoph. Soc. Inst. MDCCLXV; Prodesse Quam Conspici" inscribed.
    Class of 1857
    EX2509
    Owned by K. P. Ketcham, class of 1857.
  - Badge, circa 1765; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4813
    Cliosophic Society badge. Eight pointed star. "Clios. Soc. Instituta A.D. MDCCLXV" and "Prodesse Quam Conspici" inscribed.
  - Bronze coin, 1977; 1 box (Box E.1)
    "Republique Francaise" on front. "Senat" on back.
    Given by French delegation to President Bowen during U.S. Bicentennial year.
  - Bronze Coin, 1977; 1 box (Box E.1)
    "Victory at Princeton" NJ Bicentennial commission
  - Bronze coin?, 1946; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Bronze? 3" Coin. 1746-1946 Bicentennial. Nassau Hall on one side, U Seal on the other.
  - Bronze coin?, 1973; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Bronze? 4" Coin. James Madison Medal 1751-1836. Awarded to John Bardeen '39. Inventor of Transistor and Discoverer of the Theory of Superconductivity.
  - Bronze medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "220 Yds Run 1909" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze with a foot on a wing, "NYAC" engraved on front; "Winter Games March 16, 1909," "70 Yds Dash" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1913; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and Octagonal; seals of the United States and of Princeton, portrait of Woodrow Wilson, "Inauguration March 1913 Personal Escort Princeton Univ." engraved; orange and black ribbon.
  - Bronze medal, 1914; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze with "P" in orange and black, a man running, "11th Annual Indoor Games 1914" engraved on front; "Lap Race" engraved on back; leather strap.
  - Bronze medal, 1938; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; seals of Oxford and of Cambridge, "Oxford and Cambridge V. American Universities," "Prize Medal" engraved on front; "OandC v. PandC 1/2 Mile 1938" engraved on back.
    Mrs. Clara Pollard and Mrs. Susan A. Plum (sisters of P. R. Applegate, class of 1938)
  - Bronze medal, 1915; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round with orange and blue rims; "University of Virginia" and "1819" on front; "Virginia vs. Princeton 1915" on back; orange and blue ribbon.
  - Bronze medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze. "H" in crimson and "P" in orange and black and "Freshman 1923" on front; "Discus Throw 1923" on back; Crimson, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze; a foot on wings, "Johns Hopkins - 5th Regiment Indoor 1924 Games" on front; "3 P. D. 16 LB. Shot Put Open" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Bronze medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round; seals of Princeton and of the MIT, "Mass. Inst. Technology vs Princeton Dual Track Meet" on front; "16 Lb. Shot 1924" on back; orange and black, and red and white ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track AA" on front; "Shot Put 1924" on back; orange, blue, and black ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Shot Put 1924" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Bronze medal, 1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round; a man running, seals of Princeton and of Harvard, and "Princeton vs. Harvard Dual Meet" on front; "Javelin Throw 1926" on back; crimson, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, 1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, and "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." on front; "Shot Put 1926" on back; blue, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze, round; "Oxford Cambridge Cornell Princeton" and the seal of each school engraved on front; "International Track and Field Meet July 20th 1929 Trayers Island N. Y." on back; white ribbon; pin with "Field Judge".
  - Bronze medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Pole Vault" on back; orange and black ribbons.
  - Bronze medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Bronze with orange and black ribbons; Princeton seal. "Princeton University Open Meet". "Pole Vault HDC'P" on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; a man throwing, "Intercollegiate Association of Amateur Athletics of America" engraved on front; "100 Yds Run 1906 Ralph a. Gamble" engraved on back.
    R. A. Gamble (1909)
  - Bronze medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale. "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "100Yd Dash 1906" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; a man throwing, "Intercollegiate Association of Amateur Athletics of America" engraved on front; "100 Yds Dash 1907 R. A. Gamble" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1907; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze with a man throwing, "Jamestown Exposition College Championship 1907" engraved on front; "220 Yds Run" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1908; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Bronze and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "100 Yds Run 1908" engraved on back.
  - Bronze medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    AR.1998.036
    Bronze and irregularly shaped. Yale-Princeton "Freshman Track Meet." "220 Yds. Hurdle Low 1929" on reverse.
  - Bronze medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.18)
    for running broad jump.
  - Bronze medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.18)
    70 yard high hurdle.
  - Copper coin?, 1896; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Copper? 3" Coin. Nassau Hall on front, Latin inscription on back. Centennial?
  - Debate medal, 1902; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4480
    "Princeton Harvard Debate 1902" on front. "Won by Princeton March 26, 1902. R.W. Anthony, '02" on back.
  - Gold cross, circa 1878; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4803
    Gold Cross with "PC 78" on wine colored ribbon hanging from pin with "Nassau" inscribed.
  - Gold medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "220 Yds Hurdle 1909" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and rectangular; a man running, seal of the United States, Capitol Hill, "Federal Indoor Games 1909" engraved.
  - Gold medal, 1909; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and rectangular; a man running, seal of the United States, Capitol Hill, "Federal Indoor Games 1909" engraved on front; "50 Meters Dash" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1912; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with a man jumping, "P. U. T. A. A. Fall Handicap Meet" engraved on front; "Pole Vault 1912 Joseph M. Carey" engraved on back.
    J. M. Carey (1916)
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and irregularly shaped; "Y" in blue, "P" in orange and black, "Freshman," "Dual Meet 1923" engraved on front; "Discus" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1926; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and rectangular; a man throwing, "ICAAAA," "MDCCCLXXVI" engraved on front; "1876," "50," "1926" inscribed on pin.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and rectangular; a man throwing, "ICAAAA," "MDCCCLXXVI" engraved on front.
  - Gold medal, 1937; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and rectangular; a man readying for dash engraved on front; "1st 220 Yd. Dash 1937" engraved on back.
    Mrs. Clara Pollard and Mrs. Susan A. Plum (sisters of P. R. Applegate, Class of 1938)
  - Gold medal, 1938; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; a man's portrait [William Penn's], "Penn Athletic Club Track Meet" engraved on front; "IMI College relay Class A 1938" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1912-1916; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with "P" in orange and black, "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." engraved on front; "Pole Vault Joseph M. Carey" engraved on back; black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with a man running, seals of Harvard and of Princeton, "Harvard-Princeton Dual Meet" engraved.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; Princeton seal, a tiger on top, "Princeton Alumni Ass'n of W. PA. 38th Annual Banquet" engraved.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; Princeton seal attached; "Princeton Alumni Assn of Hudson Co. for Declamation" engraved. Watch chain charm.
    EX4896
    C. Cudlipp (1919)
  - Gold medal, 1914 May 9; 1 box (Box E.8)
    EX4902
    Gold with Princeton seal, "Western Association of Princeton Clubs" engraved on front; "Cleveland, O. May 9th 1914" engraved on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1916; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, with Princeton seal and "Western Association of Princeton Clubs" on front; orange and black ribbon with "Delegate 1916" in gold; pin with a tag inserted "Gordon Rentschler" handwritten.
    G. Rentschler (1907)
  - Gold medal, 1911; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, round, with Princeton seal and motto; "Western Association of Princeton Clubs" and "1911" on front; orange and black ribbon; gold pin engraved "Timer."
    EX4901
  - Gold medal, 1916; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. Large "P", a running man, "13th Annual Indoor Games 1916" on front; "Pole Vault" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1916; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, octagonal; Three men and "P," "V," "Princeton Virginia 1916" on front; orange and black ribbon; "Official" engraved on the gold pin.
  - Gold medal, 1921; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, round; a tiger and "Intra Collegiate Athletic Association" on front; "Upper Crew Fall 1921" on back; orange and black ribbon.
    Mr. and Mrs. Perry Morgan, Jr. (1946)
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "H" in crimson and "P" in orange and black and "Freshman 1923" on front; "16 LB. Shot Put 1923" on back; Crimson, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "H" in crimson and "P" in orange and black and "Freshman 1923" on front; "Javelin Throw 1923" on back; Crimson, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold; "Y" in blue and "P" in orange and black and "Freshman Dual Meet 1923" on front; "Shot Put" on back; Blue, orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold; "Y" in blue and "P" in orange and black, and "Freshman Dual Meet 1923" on front; "Javelin" on back; Blue, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, 1923; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold; "P","Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Javelin Throw 1923." on back. Orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, round; seals of Princeton and of MIT, "Mass. Inst. Technology vs Princeton Dual Track Meet" on front; "Javelin Throw 1924" on back; orange and black, and red and white ribbons.
  - Gold medal, 1924; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Javelin Throw 1924" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1924-1925; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, round; a tiger and "Intra Collegiate Athletic Association" on front; "Club Basketball 1924-25"on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1925-1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold, round; a tiger and "Intra Collegiate Athletic Association" on front; "Club Basketball 1925-26" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Javelin Throw 1926" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1926; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Shot Put 1926" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, 1937; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "880 YD Dash '37" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "Pole Vault" on back; blue, and orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "100 Yds. Dash" on back; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold. "P", "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." on front; "100 Yds. Dash" on back; orange and black ribbons.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold with running man; "P", "Fall Handicap Meet" on front; orange and black ribbon.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Gold and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale, "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; orange and black ribbon; pin with a tag inserted "Physician."
  - Gold medal, 1902; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with "PU" in orange and black, "Class Day Committee 1902" engraved; a pin with a black star engraved with "1902" in gold; black ribbon.
    EX4908
  - Gold medal, 1905; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with a man jumping, "P. U. T. A. A.," "Fall Games" engraved on front; "100 Yds Run 1905 Ralph A. Gamble Oct. 12th" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1905; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with a man jumping, "P. U. T. A. A.," "Fall Games" engraved on front; "220 Yds Hurdle 1905 Ralph A. Gamble Oct. 12th" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1905; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Golden with a foot on wings, "JHU," "Athletic 1905 Meet" engraved on front; "1st Prize 30 Yd Dash Interscholastic Won by R. A. Gamble Time 3 4/5" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with "P" in orange and black, "Annual Indoor Athletic Meet 1906" engraved on front; 440 Yds Run Ralph A. Gamble. March 23" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with seal of Fordham University engraved on front; "70 Yds Run 1906 March 3 Ralph A. Gamble" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with "P" in orange and black, "Caledonian Games P. U. T. A. A." engraved on front; "100 Yds Dash 1906 Ralph A. Gamble April 24" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1906; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold and round; seals of Princeton and of Yale. "Princeton-Yale University Track A. A." engraved on front; "220Yd Dash May 12, 1906 R. A. Gamble" engraved on back.
  - Gold medal, 1925-1926; 1 box (Box E.8)
    hanging from orange and black ribbon. "Intra Collegiate Athletic Association" on front. "Club Hockey 1925-26" on back.
    Given by Richard K. Paynter, Jr. '25.
  - Gold medal, 1932 May 7; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and oval. "Princeton Harvard Dual Track and Field Meet." "Broad Jump May 7, 1932" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Cornell University Dual Meet." "Princeton Run Broad Jump 1931" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and irregularly shaped with Princeton-Yale "Freshman Track Meet." Run Broad Jump 1929" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and rectangular with "1931 Columbia Princeton." "1st Princeton, NJ May 2 Broad Jump" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1930; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and rectangular with "1930 Princeton vs. North Carolina." Princeton, NJ May 10th Broad Jump 1st" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1930; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Princeton vs. Cornell Varsity Track Meet." ""Run Broad Jump 1930" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Pennsylvanis Princeton Freshman Dual Meet." "High Hurdle 1929" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and rectangular with "1931 Columbia Princeton." "1st Princeton, NJ May 2 120 Yd. High Hurdles" on reverse."
  - Gold medal, 1929; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and irregularly shaped with Yale-Princeton "Freshman Track Meet." "120 Yds. Hurdle High 1929" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Princeton vs. Cornell Varsity Track Meet." "Broad Jump 1932" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1930 May 10; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and rectangular with "1930 Princeton vs. North Carolina." "Princeton May 10th 120 Yd. High Hurdles 1st" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Princeton -Yale University Track AA." Broad Jump 1932" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.14)
    Gold and round with "Princeton vs. Cornell Varsity Track Meet." "High 120 Yds. Hurdle 1932" on reverse.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.18)
    New Jersey Association champion. 70 yard high hurdles.
  - Gold medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.18)
    120 yard high hurdle. New Jersey Association Champion.
  - Gold medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Broad jump.
  - Medal, 1913; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White and round with Princeton seal and motto; "Western Association of Princeton Clubs Indianapolis May 1913" in black; orange ribbon; a tag inserted in the pin, "Chas R. Williams."
    C. R. Williams (1875)
  - Medal, 1976; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Howard T Behrman medal for distinguished achievement in the humanities, first awarded April 1976. Misspelled name.
    6 May 1976, given to archives because of misspelled name. Gregory Vlastos was to be given the medal
  - Medal, 1894; 1 box (Box E.1)
    1894 award by to the American Whig Society to James Shaw Campbell '94.
    Given by Miss Margaret S. Campbell 11/4/60, brother of James S. Campbell.
  - Medal, 1962; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Robert Hofstadter medal 1962. AM and Ph.D. Princeton 1938, Asst. Prof. of Physics Princeton 1946-1950.
    Given to library 12 Nov 1962
  - Medal, 1912; 1 box (Box E.1)
    2". Commemorating inauguration of John Grier Hibben as President of Princeton University, May 11, 1912.
  - Medal, 1896; 1 box (Box E.1)
    10". 1896, Nassau Hall and Latin inscription.
  - Medal, 1911; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Nassau Hall hanging from two small tags with "1910" and "1911" on them, hanging from tag with "Princeton." Black and Orange ribbon with "Old Guard" on tag at top.
  - Medal, 1913; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Yellow and round with golden rim; "Commencement Committee" in black; orange and black ribbon; yellow pin with "1913" in black.
  - Medal, 1896; 1 box (Box E.7)
    A gold cross with a silver circle bearing Nassau Hall inset; orange and black ribbon with "Sesquicentennial of the Princeton College Oct. 20-22nd, 1896" in gold; a pin engraved with "souvenir."
  - Medal, 1913; 1 box (Box E.7)
    White, round with Princeton seal and motto; "Western Association of Princeton Clubs Indianapolis May 1913"; orange ribbon; a tag inserted in the pin, "Rentschler '07" handwritten.
  - Medal, 1913; 1 box (Box E.8)
    White and round with Princeton seal, "Western Association of Princeton Clubs Indianapolis May 1913" in black; orange ribbon; gold -framed pin inserted with a tag "'Doug' Pierce '06" handwritten.
    H. D. Pierce (1906)
  - Medal, 1866; 1 box (Box E.12)
    EX4810
    Cliosophic Society medal. "Facundiae Palma Danda Est" on front and "Datum A Clios. Soc. MDCCCLXVI II" inscribed.
  - Medal, 1932; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Seal in orange and black. "Annual Princeton U. Interscholastics." Discus throw 1932 on reverse. Orange and black ribbon.
  - Medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)
    Gold with gold seal and "Princeton University Open Meet." Orange and black ribbon.
    Hugh Wynne
  - Medal, 1931; 1 box (Box E.18)
    for the 60 yard high hurdle. Winged foot and branch on front.
  - Medal, 1932 February 27; 1 box (Box E.18)
    for the 60 yard high hurdle. "New York Chapter Knights of Columbus" and sailboat on front.
  - Medallion, 2010; 1 box (Box E.18)
    Streicker Bridge commemorative medallion. Round, bronze with Princeton shield and images of bridge.
    AR.2010.122
    Gift of John Streicker '64
  - Metal plate, Undated; 1 box (Box E.1)
    EX4836
    engraving of cannon with front of Nassau Hall on it.
  - Mold and plate, 1979; 1 box (Box E.1)
    Mold and plate for School of Public Affairs. 1979 Fiftieth Anniversary to Wilson speaking at Whig?
  - Reunion medal, 1910; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Iron. A circle bearing "OG" overlaid on a cross; two bars each engraved with "1910" and "Princeton"; orange and black ribbon; a pin engraved with "Old Guard." See PAW 1910/06/01.
    EX4903
    Lawrence Crane Woods (1891)
  - Reunion medal, 1936; 1 box (Box E.7)
    Red ax; orange and black ribbon with "1926 Tremendous Tenth June 1936" in gold; a tag inserted in the pin, "Geo. Cook [illegible]" handwritten in black.
    G. R. Cook, III (1926)
  - Reunion medal, Undated; 1 box (Box E.8)